Jesus is a adventure, drama, tv movie film directed by Roger Young.
Jesus, a carpenter living a simple life, discovers
his destiny as the biblical Messiah.
Jesus, played by Jeremy Sisto.
Mary Magdalene, played by Debra Messing.
Mary, played by Jacqueline Bisset.
Pontius Pilate, played by Gary Oldman.
Herodias, played by Elena Sofia Ricci.
Martha of Bethany, played by Maria Cristina Heller.
Jesus is a 1999 Italian-American biblical historical drama television
miniseries that retells the historical events of Jesus Christ.
It was shot in Morocco and Malta.
It stars Jeremy Sisto as the titular character, Jacqueline Bisset as Mary of
Nazareth, Debra Messing as Mary Magdalene and Gary Oldman as Pontius Pilate.
The miniseries was broadcast in Italy in two parts on December 5 and 6, 1999 before
being broadcast in the United States on May 14 and 15, 2000 on CBS.
The film explores themes of temple, christianity,
communion, apostle, last supper.
The tone is emotional.